你想当哪个颜色
What color would you like to be?
我想要绿色啊  可是每次都被你抢了
Well, I'd like to be green, but you know you always take it.
没有好吗
That's not true.
我哪个颜色都行
Any color's fine with me.
给我蓝色和黄色的结合色也行啊
Yeah, I could be a-a combination of blue and yellow.
蓝加黄不就是绿色吗
Blue and yellow make green.
就这么愉快地决定了
Well, then it's settled.
准备好出发了吗
Hi. Ready to go?
好消息  我们叫了午餐外送
Oh, good news, we ordered lunch,
我们可以一起在家玩《战国风云:魔戒》
so we can all stay here and play Lord of the Rings Risk.
战国风云是一种战旗类桌游  玩家用兵占领领地
再互相攻击直到征服全世界
谢尔顿  我们说好了是今晚陪你玩
Sheldon, we said that we would play games with you tonight.
没错啊  今晚我们还会继续玩
Oh, no, we'll still be playing it tonight--
这游戏花个八小时也是家常便饭
this game can easily take eight hours.
亲爱的  你真的觉得我想留下玩这个吗
Sweetie, you really thought I'd want to do this?
-没有啊  -那你跟他说了吗
- No. - Well, did you tell him that?
-有啊  -你有大声开口说出吗
- Yes. - Did you say it out loud with words?
没有
No.
我不想要一整天都留在家里玩桌游
I don't want to spend the whole day playing a board game.
你听完可能就会改变主意
Yeah, well, you may change your mind when you hear
这可是全新扩充包
that this is the new expanded edition
里面有更完整的魔戒中土世界地图
which contains a more complete map of Middle Earth,
现在还加进了哈拉德威治地区哦
now including the Haradwaith Territories.
我真的要跟你比赛谁先冲上车走人
I will literally race you to the car.
别别别  别一走了之  试试再说嘛
No, no, no, come on, don't leave. Just try it.
不要  我们总是在做你们男生想做的事
No. We're always doing what you guys want.
哪怕就一次  换你们做我们想要的事该多好
Just once, it'd be nice if you did something we wanted.
你想当绿色吗
You want to be green?
她们的确是有试着
You know, they really have tried to
喜欢上我们迷的那些事物
like a lot of the same stuff we're into.
我们参加了游戏之夜  游戏机之夜
Yeah, we do game nights and video game nights
跟你们一起看导演评论版的电影
and we watch movies with director's commentary.
我最爱的
Oh, my favorite--
是乔治·卢卡斯可以整部《星球大战》说个不停
George Lucas can talk all the way through Star Wars,
我就说一个字  就被流放到了厨房
I say one word and I'm banished to the kitchen.
今天由我跟艾米来决定我们做什么
Yeah, today Amy and I are deciding what we're all gonna do.
行啊  你们女生做决定
You got it, you girls are in charge.
-谢谢  -谢尔顿呢
- Thank you. - Sheldon?
好吧
Fine.
现在我们不玩了  绿色给你当吧
Now that we're not playing, you can be green.
-谢主隆恩  -这次你是绿色
- Thank you. - And since you're green this time,
那下次就换我了
I can be it next time.
好了  来想想  有什么好玩的事
All right, let's see. What's something fun
是他们永远不会带我们去做的
the guys would never take us to do?
我知道了  我们可以去骑马
Oh, I know-- we could go horseback riding.
我骑不了
I actually can't.
我的臀部不能打开超过22度
My hips don't open wider than 22 degrees.
我试过骑一只非常瘦的马
I rode a very thin pony once.
才颠一下  臀部就脱臼了
On the first bump... just popped right off.
好吧  那你想做什么
All right, well, what do you want to do?
威尔希尔那边有一个手工艺与民间艺术馆
There's a craft and folk art museum on Wilshire.
那是威尔希尔那边的人倒霉
Well, that's Wilshire's problem.
再想想嘛  肯定有什么好玩的事情
Come on, you know, there-there's got to be something fun
是我们想做他们讨厌的
we could do that the guys will hate.
等等  为什么非得是我们讨厌的事
Hang on, why do we have to hate it?
送你几个字  神秘博士大会
Three words: Doctor Who convention.
当时我又没逼你跟着去
I-I did not force you to go to that.
你戴着神秘博士的圆顶小帽  还别上领结出门
You walked out of the house in a fez and bow tie.
我怕你被揍才跟着去
I went so you didn't get beat up.
我才不会被揍呢
I wasn't gonna get beat up.
你差点被揍啊  是我后来突然忍住了
You were, but somehow I held myself back.
你知道你们可以逼我们干嘛吗  溜冰刀
You know what you could make us do? Ice-skating.
冷空气会让莱纳德犯气喘
The cold air will trigger Leonard's asthma
而且这正中我长久以来
and it plays right into my well-known fear of
害怕被磨冰场车压扁的恐惧
getting flattened by a Zamboni.
你在帮忙他们想能让我们痛苦不堪的事吗
Now you're helping them find ways to make us miserable?
抱歉  莱纳德
Well, I'm sorry, Leonard,
我专治各种疑难杂症  这是我强项
I'm a problem-solver, it's what I do.
我其实也不能溜冰刀
I actually can't go ice-skating.
我有非比寻常易碎的膝盖
I have unnaturally brittle ankles.
你身上有任何一个部位是正常的吗
Is there any part of your body that's normal?
我的天啊  天啊  天啊
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
-你能放轻松点吗  -我承受不了了  兄弟
- Will you please relax? - I can't take it, dude.
-你没事吧  -我有事
- You okay? - No, I'm not okay.
我感觉我灵魂快冲出我的皮肤了
I feel like I'm gonna jump out of my skin.
我就告诉你别蜜蜡除毛"那里"
I told you not to wax down there.
重新长出来的时候会痒
It's itchy when it grows back.
我在担心"新视野号太空探测器"
I'm worried about the New Horizons space probe.
于2006年发射  价值7亿美元  约钢琴般大小
在14年底从休眠中苏醒  正准备对冥王星进行探测
他在说什么
What's he talking about?
九年前他曾在一个团队里
Nine years ago he was part of a team
他们发射了探测器去搜集冥王星的资料
that launched a spacecraft to collect data about Pluto.
现在终于飞到够近了
It's finally close enough,
所以今早它自行苏醒了
so this morning it turned itself on.
是希望它会
We hope.
信号得穿越三十亿英里回来
The signal has to travel over three billion miles.
所以得过好几小时才知道它有没有成功到达
So it's gonna be hours before we know if it even survived.
所以他这副样子  就是因为他在担心
Now we get to see him flip out because he's worried
飞船在途中被太空冰给撞毁
it was demolished by space ice.
太空冰不是闹着玩的好吗
Space ice is no joke.
我现在都不敢看《冰雪奇缘》了
I can't even watch Frozen anymore.
费城爱乐在市中心演奏[玩]贝多芬呢
Ooh, the philharmonic is playing Beethoven downtown.
在你答应之前
Yeah, well, before you say yes,
1992年电影《我家也有贝多芬》
主角狗狗就叫贝多芬
她说的不是电影里的那条大狗哦
it's not the movie about the big dog.
为什么我们想不出我们俩都想做的事呢
How come we can't think of something we both want to do?
因为每次都是你选我们做什么
Because you always pick what we do
我只是跟着你
and I just go along with it.
有趣
Ah, interesting--
我们被你指控整天逼你们做不喜欢的事
we're being accused of making you do things you don't like,
结果一看  你对可怜的艾米也是这样
and here you are, doing the same thing to poor Amy.
你应该指出她的行为有多伪君子
You should point out the hypocrisy of that.
我刚才就是在说这个啊
That's what I was doing.
你说得不够清楚
Oh, that wasn't clear.
再试一次  这一次单刀直入
Try it again, but this time drive it home
并送上"自食其果了吧  小妞"
with, "How do you like them apples, missy?"
好吧  继续想
All right, keep thinking.
你干嘛把事情搞这么复杂
You're making it too complicated.
何不来点基本款折磨
Why not stick to the basics?
你们去逛街
Go shopping for clothes
我和莱纳德就坐在店里不舒服的椅子上
while Leonard and I sit in those uncomfortable chairs
帮你们看着包包
and hold your purses, hmm?
反正我是讨厌这样
I know I'd hate that.
莱纳德  你呢
Leonard?
当然
Well, yeah.
那就愉快地决定啦
Well, then, it's settled?
你觉得怎么样  听起来是个好主意
What do you say? Sounds kind of perfect.
的确  但被他这么一说  感觉乐趣都没了
It does-- somehow he managed to take all the fun out of it.
再次证明  这是我强项
Well, once again, it's what I do.
还要继续等两小时
Oh, another two hours to go.
这过程真是等死我了
The wait is killing me.
我懂这种感觉
I know. I get it.
当我坐着联盟号太空舱从空间站
When I was in the Soyuz capsule returning from the space station,
以每小时1万7千英里的速度返回地球时...
plummeting toward Earth at 17,000 miles per hour...
在你说完前
Before you finish,
我想问这故事是关于耐心和等待
is this a story about patience and waiting
还是只是为了提醒我你上过太空
or just another reminder that you went to space?
两个愿望一次满足嘛
A story can do two things.
我觉得我要心脏病发作了
Ugh, I feel like I'm gonna have a heart attack.
你在制药公司上班
You work in pharmaceuticals--
难道没有什么药可以治治他吗
don't you have anything you can give him?
我只有新出的尿流药
All I have is our new urine flow drug.
虽然缓解不了他的紧张
Won't help with his anxiety,
但药效强劲  他尿尿的时候
but it's so strong, when he pees
会像穿着喷气背包在屋子里乱飞
he'll fly around the room like he's got a jet pack.
我没有办法不去想这件事
I can't stop thinking about it.
你担心也不会改变任何事
You know, worrying won't have any effect on what happens.
我知道
I know.
或许你需要做一些更有用的事情
Maybe you need to do something more productive.
好吧
Okay.
如果这个瓶子
If I make this shot
能扔进垃圾桶
in the trash can,
就表示探测器顺利到达
the probe will have arrived
并处于能正常运作的状态
in perfect working order.
所以你除了抓狂  就只能让你的运动技能
So, in addition to being crazy, you're resting the fate
来决定这任务的命运吗
of the mission on your athletic prowess.
是的
Yes.
曾撞烂过健身固定脚踏车的超低运动技能点
The man who crashed his stationary bike.
我没有撞烂它  好吗
I didn't crash it, okay?
我的歌单节奏太快了
My playlist was too up-tempo,
音浪太强  头晕于是撞到地上
I got light-headed and I fell off.
好了
Okay.
行不行
It all...
就取决于
comes down...
这一下了
to this.
开心了吧  现在你可以放心了
You happy? Now you can relax.
你是哪门子科学家啊
What kind of scientist are you?
地球人都知道要三投两中才算
Everyone knows you got to make two out of three.
其实也没那么坏
This isn't so bad.
你说得倒轻巧
That's easy for you to say.
你的椅子又没正对着内衣物区
Your chair's not facing the lingerie section.
天啊  好多小内内哦
Boy, that's a lot of panties.
你们俩待得舒服吗  可能要等很久哦
You guys comfy? This might take a while.
我不明白为什么女人要坚持
You know, I don't understand why women insist
没完没了地买衣服
on making a big production out of buying clothes.
你说得对  我们应该向你学习
No, you're right, we should do what you do.
让自己妈妈从休斯顿寄来在超市买的裤子
Have our mom send us pants from the Walmart in Houston.
那里有个人
They have a man there
了解我的个人穿衣风格好吗
who understands my personal style.
再见啦
Bye.
我有个坏消息
Uh, I've got some bad news.
这里面没有手机信号
There's no cell service in here.
算啦  没关系
Well, that's all right.
智能手机没面世前
There were plenty of ways to pass the time
也有很多消磨时间的方式啊
before smart phones were invented.
那倒是
That's true.
我用手机搜搜
I'll look them up.
去他个小饼干
Son of a biscuit.
谢尔顿  没关系啦
Sheldon, it's fine.
不  有关系
No, it's not fine.
这都21世纪了  怎么还会有店没有无线网的
What kind of store in the 21st century doesn't at least have Wi-Fi?
我要打去他们公司总部投诉
I'm going to call their corporate office...
去他个小饼干
Son of a biscuit!
我想想啊  我的军队要袭击
Let's see, my armies are going to attack
巴克兰的一个郡[魔戒地名]
the Shire from Buckland.
我的骰子点数是
And I roll...
一个五  一个三
a five and a three.
好的
Okay.
为了捍卫家园  我的点数是
And to defend, I roll...
两个六  我赢了
two sixes. I win.
天啊  又是两个六
Boy, double-sixes again.
要不是我亲眼看见
You know... if I hadn't seen it with my own eyes,
我真不敢相信
I wouldn't believe it.
我想知道我们还要在这里待多久
I wonder how long we're gonna be stuck here.
我不知道  但她们为我们付出了很多
I don't know, but the girls do a lot for us.
这是我们该做的
It's the least we can do.
那倒是
Oh, that's true.
我想只有双方做出让步才公平吧
I suppose it's only fair we make compromises.
瞧瞧你  居然如此成熟
Look at you, being all mature.
我不懂你有什么好惊讶的
I don't know why you're so surprised.
跟你住在一起这么多年了
If there's one thing I know about after living with you
我唯一学会的事情  就是做出让步
for so many years, it's how to compromise.
你说什么
I-I'm sorry?
你为我做出让步吗
You make compromises for me?
一直如此啊
All the time.
在这个地球
On Earth?
在我们的生活中
In our lives?
在我们现在活着的世界里吗
That-That we're living?
是啊  我...
Oh, yes. I...
就在昨天  你吃午饭的时候
Just yesterday, you had a-a big piece of lettuce
牙齿上有一大片菜叶子
stuck in your teeth at lunch.
我有说什么吗
Did I say anything?
完全没有
No.
我做出让步
I compromised
闭上了我的嘴
and kept my mouth shut.
你当时也该闭上嘴  因为大家都在笑你
Like you should've, because everyone was laughing at you.
你这不是让步
That is not a compromise.
让步是我总得开车载你出门
A compromise is me driving you everywhere
因为你不肯学开车
because you refuse to learn how.
我会开车了  艾米教过我
Oh, I learned how. Amy taught me.
什么  那你怎么不自己开
What? Then-Then why don't you do it?
因为开车好可怕
Uh, well, it's scary.
有时候我会分不清油门和刹车
And sometimes I get the pedals mixed up.
但更重要的一点是  载我上班
But, more importantly, driving me to work
是你生存的意义之一呀
is one of the things that gives your life purpose.
我可不能残忍地剥夺它
I can't take that away from you,
所以  我这算是什么呢
so... what do I do?
拜托  我把答案都送到你嘴边上了
Oh, come on, I'm practically feeding you the answer.
我让步了
I compromise.
-多谢你来陪我  -乐意之极
- Hey, uh, thanks for keeping me company. - I'm happy to.
我觉得出来活动活动对你有好处
I think getting out of the apartment will do you good.
那我们这是要去哪儿
So... where we headed?
如果你不介意的话  我想去寺庙
If it's okay with you, I'd like to go to temple.
兄弟  相信我  你不会想要皈依犹太教
Buddy, trust me, you don't want to convert to Judaism.
我知道我让犹太教看起来很酷
I mean, I know I make it look cool,
但犹太教并不单纯是鸡胸肉和光明节陀螺而已
but... it's not all briskets and dreidels.
我是想去印度教的寺庙
I meant a Hindu temple.
哦  好吧
Oh. Okay.
里面不会和《夺宝奇兵之毁灭神庙》一个样吧
It's not like Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom, right?
不会有长角的光头想挖出我的心吧
Some bald guy with horns isn't gonna rip my heart out.
老兄  那部电影纯粹是帝国主义的幻想
Dude, that movie's an imperialist fantasy
把和平又善良的古国国民
that makes the followers of a beautiful and peaceful religion
意淫成茹毛饮血的野蛮人
look like a bunch of bloodthirsty barbarians.
你明明很爱看那电影
You love that movie.
是的  拍得那叫一个牛逼
Yeah, it's pretty great.
你怎么突然开始相信宗教了
I'm surprised to see you suddenly get religious.
此话怎讲
Why?
因为我认识你十年了
Well, because I've known you for ten years
你从来没去过寺庙
and you've never gone to temple,
你从没说过自己相信神
you never talked about believing in God,
上一次的印度排灯节  我亲眼目睹你在巴西牛排店
and last Diwali I watched you eat two pounds of sacred cow
吞下了两磅圣牛肉
at a Brazilian steak house.
宗教信仰是很私人的事
Religion is a very personal thing.
我是有去寺庙啊  我只是没说而已
I do go to temple-- I just... I don't talk about it.
可你是一位科学家啊
Yeah, but you're a scientist.
那又怎样
So?
身为科学家  你应该相信只有事实和证据
So, as a scientist, you believe the way to understand the universe
才是认识宇宙的唯一方法
is through facts and evidence,
怎么现在你又求助于
and now you're counting on some
长了一百只胳膊的恒河蓝妹子[希瓦神]了吗
blue chick with a hundred arms to help you?
你这么说太不敬了
That is so offensive.
你所有的印度教知识都是来自于《夺宝奇兵》吗
Does everything you know about Hinduism come from Indiana Jones?
不  还有《辛普森一家》中的印度非法移民阿普
No. There's also Apu from The Simpsons.
很多科学家都相信上帝的
Well, lots of scientists believe in God.
牛顿  法拉第
Okay? Newton, uh, Faraday,
帕斯卡  都是有神论者
uh, Pascal-- all were believers.
就连爱因斯坦也是啊
Even Einstein was famous for
那句反驳量子力学理论的名言
attacking quantum theory on the grounds that
"上帝不会掷骰子"
"God does not play dice with the universe."
他当然相信上帝啦
Well, of course he believed in God--
他跟女神玛丽莲·梦露都睡过了
he slept with Marilyn Monroe.
这事没有证据好吗
Actually there's no proof of that.
你有你的信仰  我有我的性仰
You believe in your religion, I'll believe in mine.
你试得怎么样啊
How's it going in there?
这件上班穿不太合适
Not really a great outfit for work,
除非我们新开了站街女部门
unless something opens up in the hookers and whores division.
-我能问你件事吗  -问呀
- Hey, can I ask you something? - Sure.
我真的会逼你做你不想做的事吗
Do I really force you to do things you don't want to?
是的  不过我不介意
Yeah, but it's okay.
怎么能不介意呢
How is it okay?
我发过誓  如果我能交到朋友
I promised myself, if I ever got friends,
我一定乖乖听他们的话
I'd do whatever they said.
我能在遇到邪教之前认识你  真是太幸运了
Really, I'm lucky you found me before a cult did.
可那是很久以前的事了
Well, you know, that was a long time ago.
你现在是不同的人了
You're a different woman now.
你聪明  你有很多好朋友
You're smart, you've got great friends,
你有男朋友  你也变漂亮了
you've got a boyfriend, you're pretty,
你对时尚完全没有概念  可是...
you have zero fashion sense, but...
总之  今晚你来决定我们干什么吧
Anyway, tonight we're gonna do whatever you want.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Absolutely.
你提议  我们就去做
You name it, we're doing it.
我们去手工博物馆编篮子吧
Basket weaving at the craft museum.
好吧  你都提了
Well, you named it.
我又想起了一个
Oh, here's another one.
我想把苹果煎饼粉放在架子最高层
I wish that the apple pancake mix was on the top shelf
因为苹果是以字母A开头的[Apple]
because it starts with an "A,"
但我却没这么做
but I don't put it there
因为我不想让你为我做早饭时
because I don't want you breaking one of your little legs
摔断你的小短腿
when you're supposed to be making my breakfast.
轮到我说我做出的让步了吗
Is it my turn to talk about the compromises I make?
我还没说完  不过你说吧
I wasn't done, but go ahead.
他让了一步  说道
He said, compromising.
就因为你  我不能
Because of you, I'm not allowed
调节自己家里的温度
to adjust the temperature in my own home.
也不能吹口哨
I'm not allowed to whistle.
不能穿可能会吱吱叫的鞋子
I don't wear shoes that might squeak.
你是物理学家  不是马戏团小丑
Well, you're a physicist, not a circus clown.
谢尔顿  你知道我不能和我爱的女人住在一起
Sheldon, do you realize I don't live with the woman I love
都是因为你吗
because of you?
没有其他理由  只是因为你
No other reason. Just you.
-这是真的吗  -是真的
- Is that true? - Yes, it's true.
上次我提到这事时  你精神崩溃了
The last time I brought it up, you had an emotional breakdown
跳上火车离家出走
and got on a train and ran away.
考虑到我对这事的历史反应
Well, given my history on the subject,
你现在提它是不是有点莽撞呢
it seems a little reckless to bring it up now.
你完全不知道你给身边的每一个人
You have no idea how much you inconvenience
造成了多大的麻烦
the lives of everyone around you.
我都要累死了
It's exhausting!
你知道吗
You know what?
你自以为宽容大量
You think you're so tolerant,
但事实是...
but the truth is...
你常对我很过分
you're mean to me a lot.
没错  你以为我听不出你那些冷嘲热讽
Yeah, you think that I don't notice all those sarcastic comments
看不到你猛翻的那些白眼吗  我都知道
and those eye rolls, but I do. Hmm?
我有着出色的周边视觉
I have excellent peripheral vision.
天好的时候  我连自己耳朵都看得到
On a good day, I can see my ears.
谢尔顿  如果我伤到了你  我道歉
Sheldon, I-I'm sorry if I hurt your feelings.
但这些话我已经憋了很久了
I've been holding a lot of this in for a while.
那我也道歉
Well, I'm sorry, too.
而且如果你想和佩妮住在一起
And if you want to live with Penny,
那你就去吧
then I think you should.
-你是真心的吗  -是的
- Do you mean that? - Yes.
穿好你那吱吱乱响的鞋...
Yeah, just put on your squeaky shoes and...
吱吱吱地离开我的生活
your way out of my life.
别这样  别不高兴嘛
Come on, don't get upset.
我才没有不高兴
I'm not upset.
我只是在想象没有我最好朋友的世界是如何
I'm just imagining a world without my best friend in it.
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
没关系
It's okay.
我不是要离开你的世界
I-I'm not leaving your world.
只是搬到你对门去住
I'm just talking about living across the hall.
我理解
I understand.
不论如何  我希望你了解...
Either way, I want you to know that...
我知道我有多难搞
I'm aware of how difficult I can be.
所以我只是想说...
So I just want to say...
谢谢你一直包容我
thank you for putting up with me.
兄弟
Buddy...
你们过得如何...
How are you guys getting alo...?
怎么了  怎么都哭了
What? Why are there tears?
没有事
Everything's fine.
我们刚刚在聊住所安排
We just started talking about living arrangements.
你疯了吗  你知道他有潜逃前科的
Are you crazy? You know he's a flight risk.
我也是这么跟他说的
That's exactly what I told him.
谢尔顿  我们知道你对这事很敏感
Sheldon, we know this is a sensitive subject,
你没准备好之前  莱纳德是不会搬走的
and Leonard's not gonna move out until you're ready.
要不你缓缓而离呢
Well, what if you did it gradually?
好的
All right. Well...
从每周两天晚上
how about we start with two nights a week
我住佩妮家开始
I live with Penny?
或者一晚  再加上...
How about one night and...
我让你吹口哨  怎么样
I let you whistle?
成交
Okay.
我不在家的时才能吹
When I'm not home.
说好了
You got it.
就是这样
There we go,
又让步了
compromising again.
我们真是最佳朋友
We really are the best.
就是这
Here we go,
我去的第一间印度寺庙
my first Hindu temple.
你看喷泉后面
You see behind the fountain,
看起来像角锥体的塔
that tower that looks like a pyramid?
这叫塔状室顶
It's called a Sikhara.
象征着人类和神的联系
It symbolizes the-the connection between the human and the divine.
我一直以为它是迷你高尔夫球场呢
I always thought it was mini golf.
-好吧  走吗  -好
- All right. Shall we? - Yeah.
在进去之前  有什么事
Just, uh, is there anything I should know
-你要嘱咐我吗  -比如什么
- before I go in? - Like what?
我的衣着是否得体
Like am I dressed okay?
你说真的吗  你以为你这身衣服
Really? So every other place you've been,
去其他地方就得体了吗
you thought this was fine?
我知道你压力很大
I know you're under a lot of pressure,
这事我就不计较了
so I'm gonna let that pass.
抱歉  你说得对
Sorry. You're right.
我压力太大了
I'm so stressed.
你知道吗  不管何时我走进那间寺庙
But you know what, whenever I walk into that temple
就会懂得  不论发生什么  都没关系
I realize that whatever happens, it's okay.
我们都是无边宏大的规律中的一部分
We're all part of an immense pattern,
虽然无法参透  但只要想到
and though we can't understand it, we can be happy to know
神明一直在我们身边守护便觉得开心
that it's-it's working its will through us.
说得真好
That's nice.
不管你叫它上帝  宇宙  或是自我
Whether you call it God or the universe or the self,
我们都是相互有联系的  美好的...
we're all interconnected, and that's just a beautiful...
王八羔子  那人碰到我的车了
Son of a bitch! That guy just dinged my car!
你不是吧
S-Seriously?
你打算就这么一走了之吗
Y-You were just gonna drive away?
我的生活还不够惨吗
Like my life isn't hard enough right now.
一个航天探测器可能已经毁了
A space probe might be destroyed,
我的父母正经历一场难堪的离婚
my parents are going through an awful divorce,
我的狗被剪毛的剪了个马桶盖头
the guy who cuts my dog's hair just gave her bangs!
-拉杰  -你也看到狗了
- Raj. - You saw her.
简直像《阿呆和阿瓜》里的金·凯瑞
She looks like Jim Carrey from Dumb and Dumber!
拉杰  你收到条信息
Raj, you just got a text.
探测器成功启动了  没事了
The probe turned on. It's fine.
太好了
Oh, good.
小生有礼了  老爷爷
Namaste, Grandpa.
我本以为会很无聊呢
I thought this was gonna be boring,
没想到还挺有意思
but it's actually kind of fun.
别跟艾米说  不然每个礼拜日都得来
Don't tell Amy that. We'll be here every Sunday.
谢尔顿  你这个篮子编的真不错
Sheldon, that really is an excellent basket.
这不是篮子
It's not a basket.
这是十六世纪古中国的士兵头盔
It's a soldier's helmet from 16th century China.
帅呆了
Very nice.
对  真帅
Yeah, it looks great.
我看到了
I saw that.
室友  虽然每周只有一晚
Well, roomie, it's only one night a week,
但也算是一个开始
but it's a start.
我知道  真为谢尔顿骄傲
I know. I'm really proud of Sheldon.
我也为他感到骄傲
Yeah, I'm proud of him, too.
你们能小点声吗
Can you keep it down?
外面还有人想睡觉呢
Some of us are trying to sleep out here.